thriftyniftymommy.com 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy - Thrifty Nifty Mommy

## Thrifty Nifty Mommy Privacy Policy

 _Updated 5/22/2018_

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Thrifty Nifty Mommy. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use “Services”, or when you otherwise interact with us.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the “Last Updated” date at the top of this policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as by adding a statement to our website or by sending you a notification). We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

## Collection of Information

### Information You Provide to Us

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you enter a giveaway, subscribe to a newsletter or email list, participate in an event, survey, contest or promotion, comment on a blog post, communicate with us via third-party social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us.

The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, gender, photo, and any other information you choose to provide. If you provide an email address to invite a friend to visit this site, we will collect that email address and use it to send your friend such an invitation.

### Information We Collect Automatically

When you access or use our Services, we may automatically collect information about you, including:

  * Log Information: We collect log information about your use of the Services, including your  
Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, web request, access times, pages viewed, web browser,  
links clicked and the page you visited before navigating to the Services.
  * Mobile Device Information: We collect information about the mobile device you use to access  
our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique  
device identifiers, mobile network information and information about your use of our  
mobile applications.

### Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We and our service providers use various technologies to collect information, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.

### Use of Information

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

  * Provide, maintain, improve and promote our products and services;
  * Provide and deliver the information, products and services you request and send you related information;
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and  
administrative messages;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests, and provide customer  
service;
  * Communicate with you about products, services, surveys, offers, promotions,  
rewards and events offered by Thrifty Nifty Mommy and other companies we are working with, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
  * Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or  
features that match user profiles or interests;
  * Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions, and process and deliver entries  
and rewards;
  * Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your  
needs and provide you with better service; and
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

### Sharing of Information

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy  
Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such  
information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf;
  * When you participate in the interactive areas of our Services, certain information  
you provide may be displayed to other users, such as your name, photo,  
comments and other information you choose to provide;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance  
with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies,  
or to protect the rights, property and safety of Company or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company  
assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another  
company; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.

### Social Sharing Features

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

### Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others

We may allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Company and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes by companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](https://www.aboutads.info/choices).

### Security

Thrifty Nifty Mommy takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss,  
theft, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

## Your Choices

### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability or functionality of our Services.

You can read my full Cookie Policy [here](https://thriftyniftymommy.com/privacy-policy/thrifty-nifty-mommy-cookie-policy/).

### Promotional Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by following the  
instructions in those communications or by sending an email to  
thriftyniftymommy@yahoo.com.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at  
thriftyniftymommy@yahoo.com.
